♪ ♪
♪ BLACK BEATLES IN THE CITY,
BE BACK IMMEDIATELY, TO ♪
♪ CONFISCATE THE MONEY ♪
♪ I SENT FLOWERS BUT YOU SAID
YOU DIDN'T RECEIVE EM ♪
♪ MIKE WILL MADE IT ♪
♪ THAT GIRL
IS A REAL CROWD PLEASER, ♪
♪ SMALL WORLD ALL HER FRIENDS
KNOW ME YOUNG BULL LIVING ♪
♪ LIKE AN OLD GEEZER, QUICK
RELEASE THE CASH WATCH IT ♪
♪ FALL SLOWLY FRAT GIRLS STILL
TRYING TO GET IT IN, HATERS ♪
♪ MAD FOR WHATEVER REASON
SMOKE IN THE AIR HEY BINGE ♪
♪ DRINKING THEY LOOSE IT WHEN
THE DJ DROPS THE NEEDLE ♪
♪ GETTING SO GONE I'M NOT
BLINKING, WHAT IN THE WORLD ♪
♪ WAS I THINKING NEW DAY NEW
MONEY TO BE MADE, THERE IS ♪
♪ NOTHING TO EXPLAIN I'M A
FUCKING BLACK BEATLE CREAM ♪
♪ SEATS IN THE REGAL ROCKING
JOHN LENNON LENSES LIKE TO ♪
♪ SEE EM SPREAD EAGLE TOOK A
BITCH TO THE CLUB AND LET ♪
♪ HER PARTY ON THE TABLE
SCREAMING EVERYBODY'S FAMOUS ♪
♪ LIKE CLOCKWORK I BLOW IT
ALL, THEN GET SOME MORE, GET ♪
♪ YOU SOMEBODY THAT CAN DO
BOTH BLACK BEATLES GOT THE ♪
♪ BABES BELLY ROLLING SHE
THINK SHE LOVE ME, I THINK ♪
♪ SHE TROLLING THAT GIRL IS A
REAL CROWD PLEASER, SMALL ♪
♪ WORLD ALL HER FRIENDS KNOW
ME YOUNG BULL LIVING LIKE AN ♪
♪ OLD GEEZER, QUICK RELEASE
THE CASH WATCH IT FALL ♪
♪ SLOWLY FRAT GIRLS STILL
TRYING TO GET IT IN, HATERS ♪
♪ MAD FOR WHATEVER REASON
SMOKE IN THE AIR HEY BINGE ♪
♪ DRINKING THEY LOOSE IT WHEN
THE DJ DROPS THE NEEDLE CAME ♪
♪ IN WITH 2 GIRLS LOOK LIKE
STRIPPERS IN THEY REAL ♪
♪ CLOTHES A BROKE HOE CAN ONLY
POINT ME TO A RICH HOE A ♪
♪ YELLOW BITCH WITH GREEN HAIR
, A REAL WEIRDO BLACK MAN ♪
♪ YELLOW LAMB RED LIGHT GO
THEY SAID YOUNG GUWOP N 'EM ♪
♪ JUST CAME IN THROUGH THE
SIDE DOOR ITS SO MUCH MONEY ♪
♪ ON THE FLOOR WE'RE BUYING
SCHOOL CLOTHES WHY YOU BRING ♪
♪ A MONEY MACHINE TO THE CLUB
FOR A PINT OF LEAN A POUND ♪
♪ OF WEED AND A KILO I
EUROSTEP PAST A HATER LIKE ♪
♪ I'M RONDO I UPGRADE YOUR
BABY MAMA TO A CONDO LIKE ♪
♪ CHAPO SERVING YAYO TO THE
GRINGOS, BLACK BEATLES CLUB ♪
♪ CLOSE WHEN I SAY SO THAT
GIRL IS A REAL CROWD ♪
♪ PLEASER, SMALL WORLD ALL HER
FRIENDS KNOW ME YOUNG BULL ♪
♪ LIVING LIKE AN OLD GEEZER,
QUICK RELEASE THE CASH WATCH ♪
♪ IT FALL SLOWLY FRAT GIRLS
STILL TRYING TO GET IT IN, ♪
♪ HATERS MAD FOR WHATEVER
REASON SMOKE IN THE AIR ♪
♪ HEY BINGE DRINKING THEY
LOOSE IT WHEN THE DJ DROPS ♪
♪ THE NEEDLE SHE'S A GOOD
TEASER, AND WE BLOWING ♪
♪ REEFER, YA BODY LIKE A WORK
OF ART BABY, DON'T FUCK WITH ♪
♪ ME I'LL BREAK YA HEART BABY
T AND G ON ME I GOT A LOT OF ♪
♪ FLAVOR, 15 HUNDRED ON MY
FEET IM TRYING TO KILL THESE ♪
♪ HATERS I HAD HATERS WHEN I
WAS BROKE IM RICH I STILL ♪
♪ GOT HATERS I HAD HOES WHEN I
WAS BROKE IM RICH IM STILL A ♪
♪ PLAYER I WEAR LEATHER GUCCI
JACKETS LIKE ITS STILL THE ♪
♪ 80S I BEEN BLOWING OG KUSH
I'M FEELING A LIL SEDATED I ♪
♪ CAN'T WORRY ABOUT A BROKE
NIGGA OR A HATER BLACK ♪
♪ BEATLE BITCH ME AND POLO
CORRELATED THAT GIRL IS A ♪
♪ REAL CROWD PLEASER, SMALL
WORLD ALL HER FRIENDS KNOW ♪
♪ ME YOUNG BULL LIVING LIKE AN
OLD GEEZER, QUICK RELEASE ♪
♪ THE CASH WATCH IT FALL
SLOWLY FRAT GIRLS STILL ♪
♪ TRYING TO GET IT IN, HATERS
MAD FOR WHATEVER REASON ♪
♪ SMOKE IN THE AIR HEY BINGE
DRINKING THEY LOOSE IT WHEN ♪
♪ THE DJ DROPS THE NEEDLE
THEY LOOSE IT ♪
♪ MIKE WILL MADE IT ♪
♪ ♪